

## Personal Information

FIRST NAME / SURNAME

Mitchell Barclay

**MOBILE** 

+64 27 747 2480

**EMAIL** 

mitchellbarclay2@gmail.com

References

WORK:

John Niland

MOBILE:

+64 27 759 6414

CHARACTER:

Lesley Lyver

MOBILE:

+64 27 450 1865

## Skills and Competences

**SOCIAL SKILLS** 

I am polite, friendly and easy to get along with. I have experience with customer service from customer orientated jobs at Burger Wisconsin and Countdown.

**COMPUTER SKILLS** 

I am a keen computer user and would consider myself skilled in the field. I am familiar with basic applications such as Microsoft Word and Excel, but I am also a proficient problem solver when it comes to IT. I pick up new interfaces and software intuitively and quickly, and have experience in coding HTML, CSS, Javascript & SQLite.

**ART & DESIGN** 

I am currently studying Media Design at Victoria and have had a passion for art since I was young. I have experience with graphic design, web design, illustration, 2D animation, stop-motion, as well as video design and editing. I am a competent and experienced user of the Adobe suite of applications.

My design portfolio can be found at: <a href="https://mitchellbarclay.design">https://mitchellbarclay.design</a>



## **Education and Training**

**DATES** 2015-Present

**QUALIFICATION PROGRESS** In fifth and final year

**DEGREE** Conjoint: Bachelor of Commerce & Bachelor of Design

Innovation

**MAJOR** Information Systems, Media Design

**UNIVERSITY** Victoria University of Wellington

**ACCOLADES** Included on both the Victoria Business School Dean's

List, and the Victoria Faculty of Architecture and Design

Dean's List for the year 2018.

**Work Experience** 

DATES September 2018 - Present

**POSITION** Night-fill assistant & grocery team member

**EMPLOYER** Countdown

**RESPONSIBILITIES** Customer service, stacking shelves, locating product.

**DATES** December 2018 - Present

**POSITION** Cruise Security guard

**EMPLOYER** Allied Security

**RESPONSIBILITIES** Organising passenger transport, checking passenger

ID, managing bus traffic.

**DATES** February 2018 - August 2018

POSITION Night cleaner

EMPLOYER Otis & Louie Ltd.

**RESPONSIBILITIES** General cleaning of pet daycare, prepping dogs for

pickup.

**DATES** November 2016 - February 2017

**POSITION** Commercial painter - summer position

**EMPLOYER** Terry Lynch Decorators

**RESPONSIBILITIES** Prepping/ painting interior & exterior of houses.

DATES March 2014 - October 2014

**POSITION** Kitchen help/ food counter attendant

**EMPLOYER** Burger Wisconsin

**RESPONSIBILITIES** Customer service, prepping meals, dishwashing.